

LUCHIAN CONSTANTIN

FRONTEND-DEVELOPER

I'm a FrontEnd Developer with over 1 year of experience in developing modern web applications. My skills include understanding of HTML, BEM Methodology, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Gulp as well as experience with frameworks such as Vue.js. I strive to create high quality user interfaces while adhering to best development practices. My values are efficiency, quality and continuous learning.

EXPERIENCE

O SHOP ASSISTANT, SUPERVISOR

FoxMart or. Chisinau Dacia 27, Bd.Moscova 5

2014 - 2018

- Customer Orientation
- Product Knowledge
- Team Collaboration and Communication
- · Adaptability and Problem Solving
- Positive Attitude at Work

STORE ADMINISTRATOR

FoxMart-Enter or. Chisinau , Calea Iesilor 10

2018 - 2022

- Store management
- Personnel Management
- Accounting and inventory
- Competitiveness analysis
- Excellent communication skills

TEAM-LEADER B2B

Enter or. Chisinau, Ion Creanga 6V

2022 - present

- Adaptability and problem-solving
- Commercial proposal development
- Product knowledge
- Collaboration and communication with the team
- Planning and strategy

O FRONTEND-DEVELOPER

Freelance

2021 - present

- Building pixel perfect, high quality responsive layouts through HTML and CSS and BEM
- Adding page interactions through vanilla JavaScript and Vue.js
- Using CSS preprocessors such as Sass
- Used Git as a main version control system
- Worked with third party API services such Google Maps and Open Weather
- Used Figma and Photoshop
- Used Gulp as a main bild system



+373-60-882-936



xlikelk@gmail.com



Mun. Chișinău str. Nicolae Sulac 8



instagram.com/xlikelk_



github.com/xLikeLC

SKILLS

- Teamwork skills
- Problem-Solving
- Strong Communication
- Training and self-education
- Punctuality
- Teamwork skills

EDUCATION

SECONDARY EDUCATION

Center of Excellence in Horticulture and Agricultural Technologies from Taul 2010 - 2014

HIGHER EDUCATION

In information technologies, computer science and engineering faculty (ULIM)

2014 - 2019

COURSES

COURSES - Skillbox - Frontend-

Developer 2021 - 2022

COURSES - Orange - Frontend-

Developer

2023 - now

KNOWN LANGUAGES

Romanian Advanced English Pre-Intermediate Russian Native